What else
You live here
Hope you don't mind
Tonight I walked out of the liveliest
wedding hall
That place isn't for me
I like the quiet here
It's all over the internet too
Yeah
It'll get worse tomorrow
Do you think so too
I only believe what I see
You're very clear-headed
Your place isn't what I expected
What did you expect
A bit colder
You seem like a sharp blade
Yet you dared to take me home
You're the one who brought me home
Change clothes first
The bedroom is yours
I'll sleep in the living room
Thanks I don't care what they say
They laugh at my impulsiveness
And mock me for marrying a bodyguard
But I know
Every single
decision I made today was rational
They mock you now